const daySixteenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who is the first messenger of Allah that was sent to blasphemers?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Idris",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the real name of Abu Talib, uncle of Prophet Muhammad?",
    options: [
      "‘Abdullah bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "‘Uza bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "‘Abdul Manaf bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "Hashim bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
      "Qusah bn ‘Abdil Mutalib",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the Prophets of Allaah talked from birth ( when he was born)?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Yahya",
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Prophet ‘Issa",
      "Prophet Isma’il",
      "Prophet Yusuph",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who first changed the religion of Prophet Ismail, in Mecca, and brought Idols to Mecca?",
    options: [
      "‘Amru bn ‘Aamir bn Luhayi Al Khuza’iy",
      "Hashim bn Abdil Manaf bn Qusah bn Kilab",
      "‘Aamir bn Luhayi Al Khuza’iy",
      "Abdul Manaf bn Qusah bn Kilab",
      "Qusah bn Kilab",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Prophet Adam’s height when he was created was ---- cubits tall",
    options: ["100", "80", "60", "40", "30"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When Prophet Ibraheem was thrown into the fire, all animals were quenching the fire except……………",
    options: ["Gecko", "Dog", "Bat", "Snake", "Lizard"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the First Prophet?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Idris",
      "Prophet Ilyas",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the Prophets springs of Zamzam sprouted under his leg while he was young?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Prophet Zakariyah",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Isma’eel",
      "Prophet Ishaq",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many years did Prophet Nuh spend calling his people to Tawheed?",
    options: ["1000", "950", "900", "850", "800"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Kaleemullah among the messengers of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Daud",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who are the Ulul Azm among messengers of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam, Prophet Nuh, Prophet Ibraheem, Prophet Musa, Prophet ‘Isa and Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Adam, Prophet Nuh, Prophet Ibraheem, Prophet Musa, Prophet Daud and Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Nuh, Prophet Ibraheem, Prophet Musa, Prophet ‘Isa and Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Adam, Prophet Nuh, Prophet Ibraheem, Prophet Musa and Prophet Muhammad",
      "Prophet Nuh, Prophet Ibraheem, Prophet Musa and Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Prophet Isma’eel married from the tribe of ………………",
    options: ["Quraish", "Jurhum", "Qibtiyah", "Khuzai’y", "Makka"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is called the father of all prophets of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Ya’qub",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Prophet Adam entered paradise on which day of the week?",
    options: [
      "Yaomul Jumu’at",
      "Yaomul Sabt",
      "Yaomul Ahad",
      "Yaomul Khamis",
      "Yaomul Ithnayn",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which mosque is the first on the earth?",
    options: [
      "Masjidu Adam",
      "Masjidu Qubah",
      "Masjidul Madina",
      "Masjidul Aqsa",
      "Masjidul Haram",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
];

export default daySixteenQuestions;
